["Let Me Go" playing]
[man] I'm Gurki's gay best friend.
I think that Gurki can sometimes
intimidate men
because she is just such
a stunning, confident woman.
♪ You made plans and I
I made... ♪
[woman] From Gurki, I learned that men
can be shitty.
It is hard to be a smart,
single woman in New York City.
♪ And I wished you had hurt me harder... ♪
[man] I think Gurki
does have some walls up,
but those walls come from a place
of self-protection.
♪ And I wish you wouldn't wait for me
But you always do ♪
♪ I've been hoping ♪
♪ Somebody loves you
In the ways I couldn't ♪
♪ Somebody's taking care of
All of the mess I made ♪
♪ Someone you don't have to change ♪
♪ I've been hoping ♪
♪ Someone will love you
Let me go ♪
-Hi!
-How's it going?
Good.
-You're making it up that mountain.
-This is the steepest ramp over here.
Are you Salim?
I am Salim. What is your name?
-Gurki.
-What is it?
-Gurki?
-Yes.
-I'm Bam. Nice to meet you.
-Bam?
-Yeah, like the cartoon.
-Nice to meet you.
-You look beautiful!
-Thank you! You look handsome.
-Like a special occasion.
Yeah. [chuckles]
-You ready for a drink?
-I am.
-Yeah.
-Ladies first.
Thank you.
Well, I think I may do a Prosecco.
That sounds good. I usually get rosé,
but I'll do that too.
-Two Proseccos, please.
-[man] Okay.
[man] I'll do a Miller High Life.
Miller High Life? The champagne of beers.
"The champagne of beers."
You know what's up.
-Well, I'm from Texas.
-Okay.
That's, like, beer country,
so I know my beers.
-How is New York?
-New York is good.
-How long?
-A little over two years.
-Oh, so you're brand new.
-Yeah.
-How long have you been here?
-A little over 13.
Oh, my God. So you're, like, a legit
New Yorker. 'Cause ten years, they say
-you can call yourself one.
-You get your card. I never got mine yet,
-but cheers.
-Cheers.
So you go by Bam, but your mom
didn't, like, name you Bam.
No. It's actually Roberto.
I was always in front of the TV
watching The Flintstones,
-so my first word--
-I wondered.
"I wonder if it has to do
with The Flintstones."
It was the first word I ever said.
It wasn't "mom" or "dad."
-It was "bam."
-So, where is your family from?
-We are of, like, Puerto Rican descent.
-Oh, cool.
Where are you from?
My parents are originally from
the state called Punjab in India,
which is north... North India.
I was actually born in France.
-Born in France?
-Yes.
-How'd that happen?
-I know, It's a weird story.
So, my dad, he was, like, backpacking
across Europe with a friend,
ran out of money and just decided
to join the French Foreign Legion.
-Okay.
-Then, my parents
had an arranged marriage,
so they never met.
-They met on their wedding day.
-Arrangement.
They're still married and everything.
-Tu parles français?
-Je parle français. Vouz parlez aussi?
Non.
-That's pretty good!
-Yeah, that's about all I know.
-Not bad.
-I took it in high school.
-What do you do for work?
-I started a beverage company.
I actually work
for a start-up tech company.
-That's awesome.
-My friend told me,
"Hey, get your real estate license,"
and joined a really amazing team.
I'm a SWAT officer.
So that's, like,
when some shit's going down.
-Yeah.
-[Gurki giggles]
What made you wanna join...
I come from a line of first responders.
So my father was a correctional officer,
and his brother was
a New York City police officer,
-so it was kind of a rite of passage.
-That's cool. You're living your dream.
-Yeah.
-That's awesome.
-You?
-Good for you.
I'm a buyer for jewelry
for Barneys New York,
-so... I have an MBA.
-Hmm.
So I'm very, like, business-oriented.
I like numbers and all of that.
And luckily, I feel like
I'm pretty good at it,
I have a great team that I work with.
Doing something you love
in New York is, like, rare.
When you can find the thing you're
passionate about, you never look back.
Never look back, no. I'm not
a looking-back kind of girl anyway.
So, you're, like, representing New York.
You've Statue of Liberty--
Yeah. One of the most fondest memories
of me as a child is
my mother taking my brother and I
to Ellis Island.
I just remember being
in awe of Lady Liberty.
So there's, like, five points
which represent the five boroughs.
-I actually didn't know that.
-Yeah.
-That's an interesting fact.
-A New Yorker should know that.
[Gurki]
Well, I have one tattoo.
Mine is just right here.
[Jay] Okay. All right.
-What's that about?
-Uh, it's from my parents' religion.
-Okay.
-So, they're Sikh,
and it means we're all one race sort of
thing, regardless of where you're from.
Very interesting.
Have you been to... India?
I have, yeah. Last time I went
was, like, six years ago.
-Six years? Wow.
-Yeah.
I actually lived in Israel
for about two years almost...
-Oh, cool.
-...from 2008 to 2010.
-Do you know that show Fauza or--
-Fauda.
Yeah! I watched it! It's so good.
-Everyone tells me to watch it.
-It's so good.
I did see the first episode.
I liked it because there's the whole
krav maga, because I've been learning it,
-so--
-I don't know what that means.
Krav maga, that's the martial art
that they... that they use.
-It's a very Israeli... It's very self--
-Show me a move.
[chuckles]
-Show me, like, how does it start.
-Okay. Let's do, like...
-Okay, if someone grabs you, choke...
-Okay.
Two arms around the neck and then...
there's a basic move
where you hold here.
-Uh-huh.
-And then you bring your arm over,
and then here...
-Okay.
-Then you throw an elbow...
-It's a quick one, two, and then a knee.
-So it's like...
-It's all self-defense.
-Yes.
-Gotcha.
-There's a lot of,
you know, defense from knife attacks,
a lot of gun defense.
-How old are you? Do you mind me asking?
-I am 27.
Oh, my God. You're young!
You seem mature. You don't seem
like you're some crazy 20-year-old
-or anything.
-Thank you.
You hear that? I'm mature.
You're young.
I thought you were, like, older than 30.
-Yeah.
-I'm 36.
Yeah, I'm actually... Never mind.
You look great.
Oh, thank you.
-You do not look 36.
-I am 36.
-Okay.
-Yes.
I got the gray hairs to prove it.
-They're tucked in here.
-I got the grays come in too.
-Yeah.
I actually turned 34 on Sunday.
Oh, happy birthday! Well, cheers.
Cheers. Thank you.
-Um, should we sit down and eat or--
-Sure. Absolutely.
Okay. Cool. Let's do that.
I will just...
as gracefully as possible...
climb over this bench.
[woman]
Can I get you guys a drink to start with?
I'm gonna have a vodka seltzer.
-And for you?
-I'm gonna stick to rosé.
-Rosé?
-Yeah.
She's Rosé All Day.
-Uh, I'm gonna go Bulleit on the rocks.
-Bulleit on the rocks. Okay.
That whole "Rosé All Day" thing
-drives me fucking crazy.
-I know.
Like, people have T-shirts that say
-"Rosé all day." I'm like, "Can we just--"
-But the kids now,
I say this because it's bullshit that
technically I'm still called a millennial,
but it's the things they come up with,
like "on fleek" or "lit"
or all these millions of words, like--
Although I love saying "on fleek,"
like, as a joke.
You know, I'm like, "Man, my presen--"
"I kicked ass. I was on fucking fleek."
Yeah, exactly. Wow.
So, that's a nice little leak here
hanging out with us.
[thunder rumbles]
[Gurki] I'm eating everything.
-Well--
-You don't have to eat.
Don't feel pressured to eat
because I said that.
I've to kind of catch up now.
I'm warning you that if you don't eat,
it's gonna be gone,
'cause I'm gonna eat it all.
-Listen, sharing is caring in my book.
-[Gurki laughs]
What is top on your bucket list?
I don't have one.
You don't have a bucket list?
You've never even thought...
-Really?
-No.
Bucket list means death.
-Do you?
-Oh, yeah.
-What's on your bucket list?
-I've a long bucket list. Space.
-I wanna go to space.
-You wanna go to space?
-That's crazy.
[Gurki] So, if you weren't, like,
doing what you're doing now,
like, what... If you could do
whatever you want, what would you do?
Is this like if... like just a wildcard,
-do whatever I want?
-Totally.
Oh, I'd be onstage every night
with a guitar in my hand.
-Oh, nice.You play the guitar?
-No, I don't.
[laughs]
So, how is it dating as, like, a cop?
-Ooph!
-[Gurki laughs]
-It's tough. It's not easy by any means.
-Dang! You went "Ooph."
Just because we've certain constraints
that, like...
You know, we're not allowed to associate
with known felons.
What kind of girls are you finding
that are felons? [laughs]
On a non-serious note,
do you have any, like,
weird pet peeves in, like, relationships?
-Cats.
-[chuckles]
-You hate cats?
-Uh, cats are the devil.
-[giggles]
-The girl that I dated,
she had this cat
she inherited from an ex-boyfriend,
which was weird to me to begin with.
So, like, we'd be sleeping,
and her bedroom door had a crack
at the bottom, like, this big, right?
And then it would crawl underneath.
I thought, "I'm gonna outsmart this cat.
I'm not gonna be fooled by a cat."
So then I put pillows under there. I'm
gonna jam one of her high heels in there.
And there's no way a toddler could get
this... this out of here. There's no way.
-No, cats are fucking ridiculously...
-That freaking cat figured it out.
-...agile.
-Then I said to her,
"Listen, it's either me or the cat."
She got rid of the cat.
She broke with up you...
No, she got rid of the cat.
Stayed with me. Come on.
I ain't gonna lose to a cat.
Are you crazy? Get out of here.
-No, I just...  That's a deal breaker--
-Okay, wait!
So, you made her get rid of her cat,
and then you broke up with her.
Well... it's a deeper story
than that, but...
-Okay. Let's hear it.
-We... we... Uh.
Basically, we dated for two years,
we lived together,
and I was nowhere near ready
to be a father or a husband.
I knew it wasn't fair to keep dragging
that on, so that didn't work out.
Probably my only serious relationship,
the longest relationship.
-Mm-hmm.
-Two and a half years.
But it was long-distance
really the whole time, which is not easy.
[Bam]
She really is an amazing person.
It's just... she didn't understand
what it is to have a really close family.
Like, once she saw how close
I was with my family, it just, like...
-Yeah.
-She didn't know how to react to it.
What about you?
I see you asking me a lot of questions...
-What about me?
-...about my profession...
So, like, your last relationship,
what was that about?
-So, I'm actually divorced.
-Wow!
Which is different for me.
I've never experienced that.
I was also married for a while
when I was younger.
Oh, me too.
-Really? I--
-I'm divorced, yes.
That's interesting. I was...
Love hearing that commonality.
Uh, yeah, I was...
I was very young, though.
Wait, let me tell you the thing
that most people tell you when
they say you're divorced, "I'm so sorry."
-Of course.
-Yeah.
-"I'm so sorry."
-You shouldn't be too sorry.
"Actually, it's the best thing
that ever happened to me,
but thanks anyway for your sympathy."
You know what?
No one really knows what to say.
I don't know what to say
to another divorcee.
I wanna high five. "What up?
Welcome to the club."
-"You're free!"
-Yeah!
But honestly, I have nothing bad
to say about my ex-wife.
We get along well
because I also have a daughter.
That must be, like, part of
why you seem so mature.
-Yes.
-I didn't pinpoint you for in your 20s.
When you said 27, I was like, "What?
-How?"
-[laughs] I get that. I'll...
Thank you. I appreciate that.
-How young were you when you got married?
-Twenty one.
-Oh, shit.
-21 when it was all really unfolding.
Yeah. That's even more, like,
younger than me.
Like, I was with my ex-husband.
He was my first boyfriend, so we were 17.
-Geez.
-We didn't get married till I was 25.
Then I got divorced
by the time I was your age, 30,
-and I'm now 36.
-Okay.
So I've been doing it literally backwards.
My friends joke that I'm Benjamin Button.
Is that the name?
Benjamin Button, yes.
Which is a good problem.
-'Cause I'm living life backwards.
-That's all right.
-Yeah. I've been single for a hot second.
-Hot second? That's a hot minute.
-Not even a hot second.
-Yeah, a hot week.
[both laughing]
But, um...
-[Jay] Oh, yeah.
-[laughs]
[thunder rumbling]
You said you were married. My parents
got divorced when I was 23 years old,
-and I was living here by myself.
-Really?
-It was shocking?
-It was shocking.
You think it will never happen to you,
-then it does.
-Why did they get divorced?
They were married for 23 years.
They got married when I...
They were 21 years old.
-I saw them go through good and bad--
-My parents met on their wedding day.
They had an arranged marriage.
-Isn't that wild?
-Still together?
Yeah, they're still together.
They came from a culture
where that was, like, normal.
-They had no--
-They don't have, like, a...
They're not, like, wildly in love now
at this point,
-but--
-That's terrible.
Is it terrible? I don't know.
They have me and my brother.
I want to be madly in love until I'm 85.
No, totally. I feel the same way.
But how do you feel that it's like...
like, a woman or a man has no choice in--
Arranged meaning they got to pick
who they wanted to marry, but--
You said they met
on their wedding day.
But they saw a picture.
A picture. So they basically did
a dating app and were like, "I'm all in."
Oh, my God. I never thought about that.
My parents basically, like,
-Tindered and got married.
-They swiped. Sold!
I don't know.
-That's amazing.
-That's scary.
-I cannot wait to tell my brother that.
-And they had kids.
Yeah.
So, was yours arranged?
No. It was somebody I dated in college.
Like, he was Punjabi,
which is where my family is from,
and I just knew him, whatever.
So we dated.
Um, but it was...
it was definitely not arranged.
And how long did you know that it was
not gonna be forever?
Ugh! Really early on, sadly.
-[chuckling] I know.
-You knew right away?
It was more when we started dating.
It was very taboo for, like,
people to be dating, and, like,
not have marriage as the end goal.
Like, so then you're like,
"Well, it seems kind of petty
to, like, not get married to this guy
that you've been dating for a long time
for, like, no reason."
Your parents made it work.
You should be able to make it work.
But we just weren't, like, the best
of ourselves with each other,
and I feel when you're in a relationship,
like, you wanna be the best of yourself
for the other person.
But, like, I also wasn't happy
in the relationship.
To be honest, I was kind of a shitty wife
and significant other too,
'cause I didn't know how to be,
like, a good partner.
-I was a kid when we got together.
-You know what? The fact that you said,
"I was a shitty wife or a shitty partner"
or whatever...
that's huge
'cause most people won't say that.
They'd point the finger
and be, "That guy."
-Yeah.
-"He messed up. It wasn't me.
It was him."
So that's like...
To me, that speaks volumes
that you're able to sit there and say,
"Maybe I could've been a better wife
or a partner, whatever the case may be."
Most people don't have that in them.
So, wait a minute.
You walked down the aisle
in your white dress.
I'm sure Indian weddings are a big to-do.
I've seen, like... I know what's up.
Like, you were walking down the aisle
and you're like...
Well...
No, tell the truth. Come on.
Don't "Well."
-You're fucking calling me out.
-Yeah. Say it.
Well, no.
There was a lot of pressure, for sure,
and, like, obviously, like,
my family wanted to make it happen--
You went through with something like that?
Because I've loved girls,
but I wouldn't want to...
go down the aisle
in front of my friends and family.
But I get the pressure.
I know what you're saying.
Who said they were getting a divorce,
you or him?
The final straw was, like,
he, like, cheated,
which is like, "Okay."
-That's, like, my deal breaker.
-No, I get that.
[thunder rumbling]
[Justin] Let's go back inside--
-I feel like we're gonna get rained on.
-I'm starting to get wet already.
[Gurki] Aah!
Lots of rain, let's find cover.
[Justin] Okay. Yeah.
[Gurki] This place will have more drinks,
-which you don't drink as much, but--
-After you, my lady. Lead the way.
And, yeah, I do not drink as much,
but I'm definitely a fan
of the potential...
-[chortles]
-...dance moves that we can be having.
Oh, my God. What was that?
-What was that little leg thing?
-It's a little skip-a-dee-doo.
-You just--
-Okay. So you just do that when?
-Randomly?
-Randomly.
There's also a walk you could do where
you cross over your legs and you just...
[Gurki laughs]
-[Salim] I'm gonna step to this side.
-Why?
Ah, just used to doing that.
It's the gentleman thing, stand
between you and the road, just in case.
-[Gurki] That's very nice.
-[Salim] Yes.
What if there's a crazy person
on this side?
-Then what happens?
-Well, then I'd have to switch.
-Then you'd have to improvise?
-Yes, yes.
-You make do, you make do.
-Yeah.
[Jay]
Hopefully we can do this again soon.
[Gurki] Yeah, maybe.
[Gurki] I have your Instagram handle.
-[Jay] Okay.
-[Gurki laughs]
-[Jay] DM me or something like that, okay?
-[Gurki] Sounds good.
[Bam] So, we'll definitely do this again
and... next time, we'll be more...
-uh, active...
-Cool.
...than eating all day.
-Yeah.
-It was nice to meet you.
-Yes.
-I'm gonna call a Lyft.
-All right. It was a pleasure.
-And we'll talk soon.
-Sounds good. See you.
[Gurki] This is awesome lighting.
Let's take a picture.
-[Jay] You got to the right side, right?
-[Gurki] Yeah.
This is my side.
[thunder rumbles]
Before it rains! Oh, it's coming.
-Oh, no.
-All right. Let's take one.
[thunder rumbling]
Okay. Now I'm running for it.
[thunder crashing]
[Gurki] Oh, my gosh!
Shit!
See you, Jay.
-[Justin] Whoo! Let's go.
-[Gurki] Oh, God!
All right.
-Okay. That's not open.
-[laughs]
-Ladies first.
-Thank you.
[Justin] Oh, to be dry!
[Gurki] All right.
Well, this place is fancy.
[Salim] It's very fancy.
-Thank you.
-Do you like to dance?
-Oh, man.
[Gurki giggles]
Dancing, yeah.
I'd say I'm a step above terrible.
-[chuckles]
-Step above terrible and improving.
Do you like to dance?
I love to dance. I'm also terrible,
but I don't give a shit.
-I feel you're being...
-I love to dance.
I feel you're a great dancer.
No, I'm actually really not.
So, yeah, here's the deal.
You snap, I'll dance.
-Is that fair? I'll show you--
-What does snap mean?
Like, Snapchat? Oh, okay.
[Manny] Oh, my gosh!
You millennial, you.
Can you show me an Indian move?
I will do it.
I just want to see what's the step.
Is it...
-Oh, my God.
-Give me something.
-All right. Fine.
-Yeah.
I'm trying to think.
There's this thing where it's like...
like this and then you just...
-[Manny] Kick the feet out.
-[Gurki] Yep.
-Bam.
-No, but your hands.
So you have to have one hand up
and one hand down.
-Okay.
-Then you just go like...
Pretend you're, like, my...
my girlfriend in the village,
-and you're just dancing in the field.
-That's what you're doing?
-Exactly. It's a girl thing!
-You've gathered the wheat stalks,
and now you put them down.
You do a quick move,
and you're like, "I hope someone sees.
-Is my future husband watching?"
-Yeah. Exactly.
You have two siblings.
-We're 18 months between each.
-That's intense.
Crazy, yeah.
-Do you want kids?
-Yes, definitely.
I want kids for sure.
I'm the oldest of four.
There's nothing more intriguing to me
than being a father.
Yeah.
Are you, like, wanting to have more kids?
-Do you want to focus on your daughter?
-I do--
-Are you not worried about it?
-I'd love to have...
a family, uh...
you know, with someone
that I choose to be with.
Do you want to get married again?
Marriage is a beautiful thing,
and if you find the right person,
and it works out, it's great and...
um, and then with kids, like...
-I don't know if I want kids, honestly.
-Interesting.
Yeah. Like, I would love to have kids,
but I'm also 36,
and, like, from a realistic perspective...
I don't know. It would be nice,
but I'm going to be happy with--
-Whatever happens, happens.
-Exactly, exactly.
It's a give and take,
this is what I've learned
about relationships is that...
it's not about you.
When you find that person,
you're letting a piece of yourself go.
That's not easy to do.
-Oh, my God. I don't believe that at all.
-You don't believe that?
No. I think if you find the right person,
you're not letting anything go.
-You're with somebody that accentuates--
-You've not lived here long enough.
You...
I don't think you've been in love, then.
-I've been in love.
-I honestly...
No, man. When you're--
Because when you're in love,
you put the other person first.
And now--
That doesn't mean
a part of you disappears. You're just--
How do you know?
You got divorced at 32--
-That doesn't mean I wasn't in love.
-You just told me you weren't in love.
No. I actually said I was in love,
but I had doubts.
Who says yes to getting married
-and you have doubts?
-This is called culture clash.
So this is, like, an Indian thing.
I feel you're going back--
It is. It's a very cultural thing
to not understand societal pressure
on getting married
-to somebody you've dated--
-No, I get that.
My parents had an arranged marriage.
They met on their wedding day.
You've to marry a man for life,
not your mom.
-So you're saying--
-But you lied to a man.
-You lied to a man.
-I did.
-You did.
-I was thinking--
-As long as you admit that.
-Yeah, of course!
I'm not saying I did the right thing.
I thought, "You know what? It's not--"
-You ruined eight years of your life.
-I didn't ruin it. I learned--
You totally ruined it.
You lied to him and yourself.
-Correct. I never said I didn't do it.
-You agreed
to spend your life with someone
in front of friends and family,
and it was a complete lie.
How could I ever trust you?
How would anyone ever trust you?
[sighs]
Look, I don't want you to be upset.
If you're gonna go on a date,
and you're gonna talk to me
or any guy in New York City,
I feel like they'll ask
the same questions,
because you wanna know
the true, honest answers.
You wanna know somebody from their core.
And if you can't handle that
and gonna get defensive,
-I'm asking you--
-Obviously,
we're never gonna see each other
again after this,
so I'm trying to understand,
-what you're trying to ask from me?
-All right. This was fun. I'm over this.
Good. Please.
By all means,
exit.
[exhales sharply]
[exhales deeply]
[Gurki sighs wearily]
[sniffs]
[Manny] Oh, man. What a night.
-Oh, that was a great night.
-'Cause you're such a goofball.
-It's great.
-Thanks.
-[chuckles] You're like, "I try."
-I mean,
goofball wasn't what I was going for,
but I'll take it.
-No, it's good.
-I was expecting suave, elegant, funny,
-but I guess--
-Yeah. That too.
I'm kidding. Goofball works.
I am a little bit of a goofball.
Is this my stop?
-[man] Yes.
-Cool.
-Well...
-This has been a pleasure.
-Let me get your Instagram.
-Can I get your number if that's okay?
-Sure.
-A little more official.
-I'd like that if you wanna put it in.
-Okay.
What are you doing this weekend?
I am probably sleeping in this weekend.
[Gurki] I loved meeting you.
You're amazing.
No, you.
"You hang up."
"No, you hang up."
Thank you so much again.
-See you.
-Have a good night,
morning, night, morning.
[laughs]
Oh, my God.
["Sit Still, Look Pretty" playing]
♪ Could dress up to get love ♪
♪ Guess what? ♪
♪ I'm never gonna be that girl ♪
♪ Who's living in a Barbie world ♪
♪ Could wake up and make up ♪
♪ And play dumb ♪
♪ Pretending that I need a boy ♪
♪ Who's gonna treat me like a toy ♪
♪ I know the other girlies
Wanna wear expensive things ♪
♪ Like diamond rings ♪
♪ But I don't wanna be the puppet
That you're playing on a string ♪
♪ This queen don't need a king ♪
♪ I don't know what you've been told ♪
♪ But this gal right here's
Gonna rule the world ♪
♪ Yeah, that is where I'm gonna be ♪
♪ Because I wanna be ♪
♪ No, I don't wanna
Sit still, look pretty ♪
♪ You get off on your nine to five ♪
♪ Dream of picket fences
And trophy wives ♪
♪ But, no, I'm never gonna be ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't wanna be ♪
♪ No, I don't wanna
Sit still, look pretty ♪
♪ You get off on your nine to five ♪
♪ Dream of picket fences
And trophy wives ♪
♪ But, no, I'm never gonna be ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't wanna be ♪
♪ No, I don't wanna
Sit still, look pretty ♪
♪ Sit still, look pretty ♪